Today I'd like to give you a
detailed analysis of Elon Musk's Grock neural network
.  To access this
neural network, enter
grog.com in the browser's address bar.  Important
clarification.  This site can only be opened
via VPN.  To start using
this neural network, we need to either log into
our personal account or
register.  If we click the
registration button, the network
will offer us several options on
how we can register.  Either
through an account on x.com, formerly
Twitter, or through email, an
Apple account, or a Google account.   The most
inconvenient way to log in is via
Google email, so I'll register.
So, after we
have registered or logged into our
account, we are taken to the main
screen of our neural network.  Let's go
through the menu and the main buttons we have
here.  The menu for this neural network is
located on the left side, and we have a
total of six buttons here.  What can they do?
If we click search, a
window will open in which all our dialogues will be stored
, and through the search window we can
find the dialogue we need.  Since we have a
new profile, we don’t see anything here
.  It says: "History is empty."  For now,
we'll close this window.  And with the second
button we see the chat.  If we click on it
, our
main window opens, in which we enter a
request.  The third button is voice.  If
you know English well and can
communicate in it, the browser will prompt you
to turn on the microphone, and you will be able to communicate
with this neural network using your voice.
Our fourth button is Imagine.   The
Imagine button is responsible for creating
images and videos within this
neural network.  At the bottom there is a window for
creating a request and items for
setting functions and adding files.   A
project folder is something like a bot
that stores specific
instructions so that you don't have to write them down
constantly, but can use the project
and create
new tasks based on the instructions.  And the history button stores
all, again, our requests that we
created earlier.  Let's create a new
chat by clicking on the chat button.
Our main window opens.  What
buttons do we have here?  There is a
private button.  If we click on it, the
neural network will tell us that this chat
will not be displayed in your history and
will not be used for training
models.  This means that if we do not
want to share the data that we
write to this neural network, then we press
this button.  If it doesn't bother us in any way
, then we simply don't touch it and
continue using the neural network.  What
functionality do we have here?  If we
click on the paperclip, we will notice that we
have the option to upload a file,
add text, draw a sketch,
connect a Google Drive or Microsoft
OneDrive.  There is also a section called
recent files.  It will show the
uploaded files that were
previously added to the neural network.  Next
comes the request window.  Here we write the
request we want to give to this
neural network and receive a response.  The next
button that goes to this neural network
is the choice of how long the
neural network will think.  We have four
modes: auto, fast, expert and player
4.1.  If we choose a car, the neural network
itself will decide whether it needs to analyze
the data quickly or slowly.  The button
quickly gives the fastest possible answer,
but it will be as superficial and
standard as possible.  If we click on the
expert button, it will be a more detailed
study with more precise data and a
more specific conclusion.  Rock 4.1 is the
most advanced model that
strives to combine both speed
and precision.  We also have
supergrok and custom settings.
Supergrok is now available for subscription.
There is no free version available.
Individual settings, if we click
configure, which will be the response option
from the neural network.  We can choose
custom, laconic, formal or
Socratic style.  I don’t touch anything here
and just close it with a cross.
So, let's ask the very first
question.  Hello, who are you?  To send
a request, we click on this
arrow.  And at the same second, Nerosek
tells us that this is Nerosek 4 and was created by the
XAI company.  What can we do with
the response that the
neural network sends us?  We can
regenerate if we don't like the answer.  We
can voice it, start a discussion,
copy, share this answer and
give the neural network instructions on whether to like it or
not.  If we click on more, then
here we will be able to report a problem,
export PDF, create a
share link.  Next comes the context.
If we want to develop this topic further, Neroset
offers us some question options.  If
we click here, then, in fact, we
will have a new dialogue.  As we can see, we now have a
window to receive notifications
when the player finishes responding.  This means
that if we click the enable button and
switch to another browser tab,
we will receive a notification that
the network has finished working and will show us the
completed response.  And now the neural network has given
us the answers.  Also, if we want
to know where the neural network got its
information from, we can click on
30 sources here.  A window will open on
the side, showing us where
the neural network got the information.  We can
click on the web search, and all
the sources from which the neural network obtained
information will open.  We can click on any one and
see what source was
used.  And now let's try to
work with files.  So I've chosen
the photo I want to use.
As we can see, it appeared in
this window.  If we have chosen no, we
can click on the cross.  And as we can see,
we now have a button to edit
the image.  If we click on it, a
window will open in which we can
set instructions for this image.
We have an option to make a video.
creative background and theme.  Let's say I want to
make a request like this.  And I won’t post anything here
.  I'll just send it the way
I wrote it.  I click on the arrow and
we get two photos with the
repainted shirt.  But it's not really
green, but more of a khaki color, but
overall it's still good.  So what can we
do with these photos next?
If we look at the button above,
we can simply download this photo.
Or we can click the
play button.  We will get a
pop-up window that says
make a video.  If we click on it, a
photo will appear in which
we can also change
the image again or write a prompt in
which we want to indicate what should
happen.  Let's say I write, I write a
man turns his back and looks
at the mountains.  And to generate the video, I'll
click on this white arrow.  So,
our video is ready.  And what's interesting is that this
video is created with voice-over.  If
I click on it, we can see the
result that the neural network produced.
If we liked the video, we can
click this button to download it,
or this button to create a
share link.  Let's say we've done
everything we need to.  Click on this
back arrow.  It was about creating
an image and working with it within a
dialogue.  If we want to create a photo or
video directly in the editor, we
click the Imagine button and get to the
window in which all photos and videos are created
.  To select photo or
video mode, here at the bottom, where the
dialog box is, there is an image
or video button.  We choose what we want to
do.  And here we have the
aspect ratio.  Either vertical 2:t, or 3
:2 is horizontal, and 1:O is
square.  Let's say I want to make a
vertical video.  I press 2:t and
select video.  And in this video I will write,
let's say, I will have a request like this.
I click on the arrow and the video starts generating
.  Additionally, while our video is being created
, we can scroll down and
see other options
created by this neural network, but from
other users.  So, our video
has been generated, we can watch
it.
Now let's try to create a video
with text.  I am writing a similar
prompt again, but I am finishing it.  I finished writing
and said a colon and put it in quotation marks:
"Happy New Year, friends."  I click
on this arrow again, and we start
generating the video.  While the video is being created,
I would like to point out that the free
plan has a very limited number of
generations, both photos and videos.
By 2025, the limits for photos are around 10
dash-15 images and videos are about the
same.  If you buy the paid
version, you will receive about 3050
within 24 hours.  This works for both
free and paid plans.
Meanwhile, our video has already
been generated.  Let's take a look at it.
Will the neural network give us video
along with text?   Happy
New Year, friends.
As we can see, the non-rosset also added laughter to
our grandfather.  If we want to create a
picture, then we go back to imagine.
And in this section we select not a video,
but an image.  What other interesting
features does Ugrok have?  If we click on
deep search, we will automatically enable the
deeper exploration function.
Here we have the mode automatically
switch to expert.  And to show the
difference, let's turn it off now.   Here
I will put it on quickly.  And
let's make this request.  And to
compare, I will ask this
strange, but at the same time unusual question.
Why are apples healthier than candy?  And I press the
arrow.  And here the Neural Network wants to
offer us the options that we
like best.  Let's say I
liked this option.  But if I
copy this query, create a new
chat and click Deep search, paste the query
again and click the arrow, then our network
starts to think much deeper
and for a longer time.  This is where the
analysis process takes place.  The only thing left for us to do is
wait for a ready
answer.  Literally a couple of minutes passed.
The neural network analyzed everything and started
giving me some kind of huge
answer with various links to and from the
resources that he used.
I scroll further.  There are some
numbers, various tables that he
gives us, and a huge number of
arguments for and against the topic that
we asked him.  And at the very end, he also
leaves a list of the resources
he refers to.  So, we have
our detailed generation.  And now,
look, we can click on these three
dots and click export to PDF.  And
let's see what the neural network formed
from this text.  So, I opened the finished
file and got our text, which was
given to us by the neural network.  And let's go through the
rest of the points that are in this
neurota.  This is the very first
search button I was talking about.  If we
click on it now, we will see all
the queries that were created throughout the
entire video.  We can choose any one and
go to it.  We can also
share it here, rename it, or delete it
if we don't need it.  To close this
window, we simply click on an empty
space.  We also have a
story here.  If we click on it, we
essentially see the same thing.  But if we don’t
want to go to the search, then we
simply open a menu on the side,
where we can select the dialogue
we need.  Now let's
look at such a thing as projects.
To help you understand it better, I'll just
show you an example of how it all
works.  I click create project.  A
window appears in which I will write.   The
project instructions contain a window in
which we record all the details
that must be present during generation in a
specific project.  I won't go
into great detail now, I'll
just show you the logic.  You create a
script for YouTube videos.  I click
next.  Project files.  We can
upload some instructions here in the form of
documents, or some files on the
basis of which we will work.
I don't have such files now, but you
can
add any files
you have by clicking the attach button.  This is also done either by
uploading a file, or by connecting to
Google Drive or OneDrive.  I
won't add anything, I'll just click done.  A
window opens with our assistant,
on the right side below we have a
window for a request.  I write and click on this
arrow.  A request is sent to
the neural network, and we receive a ready-made
result in the form of a script.  We have a
short description of our future video.
These are duration, style, purpose and
monetization.  The script itself is broken down into
an intro, what a player is, and key features.  And
then everything goes according to the scenario that the
neural network itself came up with.  To understand the
main principle, here in the instructions
you write down the logic, how
the neural network should respond and what
functions it should perform.  And here in
the window you write only what you
specifically need to receive.  That is, in
essence, this is your assistant who
performs a specific task for
specific purposes.  And we are left with a menu
that is located at the bottom.
If we click on the arrow here,
our menu will appear here, which
contains both history and projects.
also pictures, voice, chat, that is, everything that
we used throughout the
video.  If we click on our icon, a
menu will open directly for
our profile and our specific
settings.  Click on the settings button,
and the main points
available in this neural network will open.
Our data is written here.  Upgrading to SuperG
is a subscription upgrade.  X account -
we can link our account from
Twitter or X, change the language if
the system has identified it incorrectly.  And
here again we are offered to increase our
subscription.  In the design section, select
light, dark, or the system theme that we have
installed within our operating
system.  Transferring long terms for code
and default blocks is a feature
needed by programmers.  Yes, a non-Rosnet
player can also write code.  You can
easily create these requests for her,
show conversation previews in
history, and turn on a star background.  This is
more for decoration.  This
function does not fundamentally affect the answers in any way
.  behavior, enable
autoscroll if you need it, or if
not, enable the back panel editor
for code.  That is, it’s all more for
your work, for your comfort.
Personalization, I already talked about it.
Here you choose the style in which the player
should communicate with you, so that the answers you receive
are as pleasant as possible.  And in the
data management there is a section to improve
the model if you want to feed your
data into the growler so that it can
learn better.  Customize your chat experience
using your conversation history,
view deleted conversations, clear the
cache, and export account data.  And
if you have a lot of files, click the
button, and your photos and videos will be
exported to your device.  Also
delete all chats and delete account.   The "
Upgrade Plan" button opens all the
pricing options available for this
neural network.  There are basic ones, super-grok
and super-grok heavy.  The main difference between them
will be the number of tokens you
will be given per month and the number
generated per day.  If, for example,
you can take around 10 pictures and videos throughout the day on the free
plan
, then, for example, on
Supergrok you'll have a limit of around
200-300, and if Supergrok is heavy, it
could even reach 500. Also
mentioned here is the expanded access to CROC 4.1, and the
expanded access to CROC 3 is
the automatic acquisition of the most advanced
model from this neural network.  And with SuperG
Heavy, you'll also get the most
advanced developments that
this neural network has.  In parallel, there will also be the
longest memory, 256,000 tokens.
This means that if you create one
window per request, the amount of memory for
this request will be up to 256,000
tokens.  This means that the neural network will not
get confused, but will constantly move forward,
respecting the context that we set
from the very beginning.